玛蒂
Maddie.
嘿  丽芙
Hey, Liv.
你来有何贵干
What are you doing here?
我来接你去参加那场比赛
Well, I'm here to take you back to the game.
不过这是怎么回事
But what is all of this?
哦  你可是说对了
Oh, you were so right.
我可喜欢这双鞋子了
I love these shoes!
哦
Oh!
这事情我们可以稍后再谈
Well, okay, we can talk about that later.
你先把这双鞋子脱了  我这就要接你去参加比赛
Just kick those off and we will get you back to the game.
噗  我才不去什么比赛咧
Pfft. I'm not going back to that game.
你到底是谁
Who are you?
我是一个喜欢穿高跟鞋  闪闪发亮的软妹子
I am a shoe-loving sparkly girl.
你要不要和我一起模仿那些超模啊
Do you want to play supermodel with me?
呵呵
Yeah.
当然了
Of course I do.
停  停  停  停
No no no no.
这  这腔调不对
This... this is wrong.
玛蒂整个失控了
Maddie was out of control.
呼  这个任务看来比我想象的困难多了
Whew, this was a much bigger job than I thought it was going to be.
我肯定是要找后援了
And I was definitely going to need backup.
不过
But first...
行  就一分钟
Okay, one minute.
好的
Yes.